quiz_data = [
  {
"question": "Who is the current captain of the Indian cricket team in Test matches?",
"choices": ["Virat Kohli", "Rohit Sharma", "Ajinkya Rahane", "Cheteshwar Pujara"],
"answer": "Rohit Sharma"
},

{
"question": "Which player holds the record for the highest individual score in Test cricket for India?",
"choices": ["Sachin Tendulkar", "Virender Sehwag", "Rohit Sharma", "Virat Kohli"],
"answer": "Virender Sehwag"
},

{
"question": "Who is known as the 'Wall' in Indian cricket due to his solid batting technique?",
"choices": ["Rahul Dravid", "Sachin Tendulkar", "VVS Laxman", "Sunil Gavaskar"],
"answer": "Rahul Dravid"
},

{
"question": "Which Indian cricketer has the highest number of centuries in One Day Internationals (ODIs)?",
"choices": ["Virat Kohli", "Sachin Tendulkar", "Rohit Sharma", "MS Dhoni"],
"answer": "Sachin Tendulkar"
},

{
"question": "In which year did India win its first Cricket World Cup?",
"choices": ["1983", "1987", "1992", "2011"],
"answer": "1983"
},

{
"question": "Who is the highest wicket-taker for India in Test cricket?",
"choices": ["Anil Kumble", "Kapil Dev", "Ravichandran Ashwin", "Harbhajan Singh"],
"answer": "Anil Kumble"
},

{
"question": "Which Indian cricketer has the nickname 'Hitman'?",
"choices": ["Rohit Sharma", "Shikhar Dhawan", "Hardik Pandya", "KL Rahul"],
"answer": "Rohit Sharma"
},

{
"question": "Who is the current head coach of the Indian cricket team?",
"choices": ["Ravi Shastri", "Anil Kumble", "Gary Kirsten", "Duncan Fletcher"],
"answer": "Ravi Shastri"
},
{
"question": "Who is the highest run-scorer for India in Twenty20 Internationals (T20Is)?",
"choices": ["Virat Kohli", "Rohit Sharma", "MS Dhoni", "Suresh Raina"],
"answer": "Virat Kohli"
},
    {
        "question": "Who is the current captain of team India?",
        "choices": ["Rohit Sharma", "Virat Kohli", "M.S.Dhoni", "Hardik Pandya"],
        "answer": "Rohit Sharma"
    }   
]